International Union of Immunological Societies records
International Union of Immunological Societies records
- Series V. Affiliated Organizations, 1972-2000; 3.5 boxes (4 linear feet)
  - Subseries V.B. International Training and Research Center (ITR), 1977-1980; 1 folder
    Contains the organization’s charter, reports and correspondence.
    - 1977-1980 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Subseries V.C. World Health Organization (WHO), 1972-1973, 1991-1999; 4 folders
    Reports, correspondence, and memos in date order.
    - 1972-1973 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - 1991-1993 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - 1993-1995 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - 1996-1999 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Subseries V.D. International Council of Scientific Unions (ICSU), 1973-2000; 3 boxes (1.25 linear feet)
    Correspondence, audits, reports, grants applications, and newsletters are arranged in alphabetical order by subject and then in date order.
    - Audited Accounts 1994-1999 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence 1973 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1974 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence 1975 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence 1976 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence 1977 (Jan - Jun) (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence 1977 (July - Dec0 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence 1978 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence 1979 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1982-1983 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence 1984 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence 1985-1987 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence 1990-1995 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence 1996-1998 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence 1999-2000 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Dues 1992-1994 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Exchange Rates 1978 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Exchange Rates 1979 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Exchange Rates 1980 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Exchange Rates 1992-1998 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Grants 1985-1987 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Grants 1988 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Grants 1986 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Grants 1990 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Grants 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Grants 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Grants 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Grants 1997-1999 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Newsletters 1980-1985 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Reports 1992-2000 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Subseries V.E. Miscellaneous Organizations, 1981-1998; .5 box (.25 linear feet)
    Reports and newsletters in alphabetical order by subject
    - Asian Network for Biological Science 1984 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - International Biosciences Network Reports 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Newsletters 1981-1983 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Reports 1981-1984 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Series VI. Oversized, 1 box
  - 1995 Conference Textiles (Originally Box 33, Folder 9) (Box 49)